Guide to the Samuel R. Delany Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Samuel R. Delany papers
1942-2015
JWJ MSS 184
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
235.17
(278 boxes) + 1 record album storage, 7 art
The collection consists of writings, correspondence, personal papers, printed material, photographs, artwork, professional papers, audiovisual materials, electronic media, and other papers documenting the work and life of Samuel R. Delany. Writings include drafts, corrected proofs, and fragments of many of Delany's books, including The Einstein Intersection (New York: Ace Books, 1967), Dhalgren (New York: Bantam Books, 1975), and Phallos (Whitemore Lake: Bamberger Books, 2004). Correspondence includes both family and professional correspondence, as well as fan letters. Correspondents include Marilyn Hacker, Iva Hacker-Delany, Robert S. Bravard, Camilla Decarnin, Thomas M. Disch, and Joanna Russ.
Delany, Samuel R., 1942-
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of writings, correspondence, personal papers, printed material, photographs, artwork, professional papers, audiovisual materials, electronic media, and other papers documenting the work and life of Samuel R. Delany. Writings include drafts, corrected proofs, and fragments of many of Delany's books, including The Einstein Intersection (New York: Ace Books, 1967), Dhalgren (New York: Bantam Books, 1975), and Phallos (Whitemore Lake: Bamberger Books, 2004). Correspondence includes both family and professional correspondence, as well as fan letters. Correspondents include Marilyn Hacker, Iva Hacker-Delany, Robert S. Bravard, Camilla Decarnin, Thomas M. Disch, and Joanna Russ.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Henry W. Wessells IV on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund and the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 2017, and gift of Samuel R. Delany, 2017.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: May 2017 Acquisition; and September 2017 Acquisition.
Samuel R. Delany
Samuel R. "Chip" Delany, born 1942, is an African American writer and literary critic whose work spans science fiction and memoir, often addressing themes related to sexuality. A winner of four Nebula and two Hugo awards, Delany was inducted into the Science Fiction and Fantasy Hall of Fame in 2002. He was married to poet Marilyn Hacker from 1961 to 1980. They have a daughter, Iva Hacker-Delany.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
September 2017 Acquisition: In-process material. Research use may require advance notice. For further information, consult Access Services.
Box 247: Restricted until 2073. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Box 248: Restricted until 2060. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Boxes 244, 246 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 245 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
African American authors -- 20th Century -- Archives; American literature -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Gay authors; Science fiction, American; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photographs; Authors, American -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bravard, Robert S.; Decarnin, Camilla; Delany, Samuel R., 1942-; Disch, Thomas M., 1940-2008; Hacker, Marilyn, 1942-; Hacker-Delany, Iva; Russ, Joanna, 1937-2011
- May 2017 acquisition, 200.17; (249 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Henry W. Wessells IV on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund and the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 2017.
  Custodial History
  The bulk of these materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University.
  - Materials deposited in 1974 and 1975, 1950-1975; 12.08; (28 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in 1974 and 1975.
    - Manuscripts, 1950-1970
      - Novels, 1961-03-1968
        - Babel-17, 1965-07-16- (Box 1)
          Scope and Contents
          Contains: typescript draft with corrections.
        - The City and the Sea, undated; (14 folders) (Box 1)
          Contains: multiple typescript drafts with corrections.
        - The Einstein Intersection, 1966-07- (Box 1)
        - Empire Star, 1965-09- (Box 2)
        - The Flame of the Warthog, 1961-03-; (2 folders) (Box 2)
        - The Jewels of Aptor, 1962-02- (Box 2)
        - Lon and Afterlon, undated; (5 folders) (Box 2)
          Contains: typescript drafts with corrections.
        - Lon and Afterlon, undated (Box 3)
        - The Lovers, 1961-01- (Box 3)
        - Nova, 1966-06-1967-05; (3 folders) (Box 3)
        - Nova, Circa 1967-1968 (Box 4)
          Contains: galley proof.
        - Those Spared by Fire, undated; (3 folders) (Box 4)
      - Short stories, undated
        - Short stories, undated; (6 folders) (Box 4)
          Contains: typescript and holographic drafts. Includes: "The Adventures of Kelly"; "Apres Le Deluge"; "An Informal Essay"; "And then he was running. The..."; "At first it was like being lost..."; "Beginnings****Three things happened at the..."; "Bozus stood looking at the..."; "Casting Out Nines"; "Chapter 1: assignment"; "Chad walked onto the ship. His..."; "The Children"; "Chuck, the three level idea is..."; "class room. The four pictures..."; "copies so as not to offend someone..."; "Did You Ever Throw a Penny..."; "Entitled An Anachronistic..."; "A Fancy"; "The First and Second Galaxies had long..."; "The first boat landed, and then a million..."; "Found in a Bottle"; "From over the hill he could see..."; "From the Mountain"; "From the Sea"; "Gramps was in the rerest of rere..."; "Gravedigger"; "Gypsy"; "hands down, angled thighs,..."; "He believed there was magic and..."; "He came from the mountains. He..."; "He couldn't do anything about it..."; "He observed the word from his bland..."; "He walked in a loose jointed, almost..."; "Hoad"; "Horson was standing in the door. All..."; "Hosf Klien stood under the shadow of...".
        - Short stories, undated; (6 folders) (Box 5)
          Contains: typescript and holographic drafts. Includes: "I am sitting on the train talking..."; "In a dirty, run down section of a small..."; "In Mourning Becomes Elektra, O'Neil's..."; "In which: our story begins, - where we..."; "The Inner Flame"; "It had once been a good neighborhood..."; "It wasn't really fair because I'd..."; "It's very rare to know two people..."; "Jude the Obscure"; "just lay there thinking..."; "Johnny ran as fast as his ten-year-old..."; Kr. stood at the window looking out..."; "A lion roared and drums made it..."; "The Little Man from the 3.141...Dimension"; "The Lower Depths"; "The Man Who Smelled of Lion"; "Marra"; "Mary, Queen of Scots"; "...meticulously phrased tones, easily..."; "A maniacal landscape that gorged..."; "Mike, Jesus, and Me"; "Mutant"; "New York City 1999"; "Newport Jazz Festival"; "Night swept across Ister like..."; "Night of the Wild Horses"; "Now I am part of the mattress. Her..."; "On slashed streets the night..."; "Once upon a time, in a place quite..."; "One great emrald jewl sprawls..."; "Our time fosters two..."; "Out of the Dead City"; "Palimpsist"; "Passacaglia, With Death in Higher Voices"; "Part One: The Vigile of Stars"; "The Pathetic Exploration of the Tragic Problem"; "...peration for an epileptic fit. But..."; "Piece of Mind"; "Piscium"; "...the poet. Rereading again, we see, no, these things only..."; "Pools"; "Portrait of the Artist as Three Characters in Search of Tea and Sympathy"; "A rollicking old tune that was..."; "The Saphires of the Sun"; "The Silver Saint"; "Silence"; "The Select Lunchroom was on the..."; "The Scorpion's Logue"; "School was a twelve year interruption in my..."; "Small Forray into the Way Things Are"; "A small girl child not three touched..."; "The Sound of the Moon"; "Sillent Monologue For Lefty"; "...sunset rouged the rocks around them.) The..."; "Tommy was the perfict proof that..."; "There've been 44 expidionts to the moon..."; "Then cease this inecent bable and let..."; "The Torture Garden"; "Through All Your Windows"; "Thud and Blunder type story"; "'This is highly irregular!' she..."; "thibk os some clever quip to brake..."; "The Tragedy of Ophelia"; "'The trouble,' Dr Ray said, 'is that you...'".
        - Short stories, undated (Box 6)
          Contains: typescript and holographic drafts. Includes: "We screamed. His hands extend, trying to house..."; "was because of its ideal location. It..."; "A Wisp of Night"; "The World of Null"; "The Witch Master"; "Under the white sky, someone grabbed..."; "The time cycle was completed - or should I..."; "'Yes. I do.' She handed it across...".
      - Film scripts, undated (Box 6)
        Contains: typescript drafts. Includes: "Fugue for Many Voices"; "Opening shot: Sky, pan down to tops of..."; "(When the film starts, we are not sure weather...".
      - Plays, undated (Box 6)
        Contains: typescript and holographic drafts. Includes: "Bare stage; our scene is the theatre of..."; "A vacant lot"; "Boss Island"; "The Coming"; "Everycat"; "Farce of Proteus"; "Fire"; "Hop Frog"; "How Green the Corn"; "Joey"; "The Men Between"; "Murder in the Mess Hall"; "Ros: Do you know what it..."; "The sceen is of a dirty room in a..."; "Scene: a blank stage wich will come out latter..."; "She lay still on the filthy floor with the..."; "Silences"; "Snake: (Softly.) Suppose he killed you..."; "Songs of the Apteryx"; "The Sound of the Flute and Lyres"; "A State of Revolution"; "The Stranger Beast"; "Sun*Dark"; "They Shall Not Pass"; "Tortilla Flat"; "Walpurgisnacht"; "The Wayward Wind".
      - Poetry, 1956-1960, undated; (3 folders) (Box 6)
        Contains: typescript and holographic drafts. Includes: "a,b,a,b,b,c,dc,c The golden sheres are drooping..."; "about the doctor on the fourty ninth..."; "After Carmina Catulli"; "Ana's Travelin'"; "...and being in our hands..."; "...and blood. Any myself already scarlet,..."; "...and exults with the thought if..."; "And I screamed at her downward,..."; "And where an ancient world layed down..."; "Atlantis"; "Attempts to regulate fall flat as old..."; "The Ballad of Pritchard Bleary"; "The Ballad of the Wandering Jo"; "Ballade de L'enfant Prodigue"; "Billie from the Tower"; "Blind Seeds"; "But turn away or 'tis your lot..."; "Canticle for Ephesus"; "Canzone"; "Casting Out Nines" with illustrations; "Catullus 5"; "Charcone"; "Choruses, Agons, and Fragments from 'Antigone'"; "Ciudades!"; "Combinations and Permutations of Melesande and Carry Rienstien"; "The coming of spring is..."; "Contemplations of Perfidy"; "The countryside was cold and still..."; "Cycle"; "Dear Mr. Edw. Greer, dear..."; "Did I say..."; Down"; "Eclogue the First"; "El Rey de Harlem"; "Elegy for Janis Joplin" by Marilyn Hacker; "Epilogue to Perseus"; "The Escape of Old John Wed(T) (?)"; "Epithalamia"; "Fragment"; "Go Down, Ol' Hannah"; "Hank: 'Pleased to the last, he crops..."; "He saw me not, nor did he wish to see..."; "Helen"; "Here in the winter garden with my..."; "Hiakiki, Tanka, Cinquaus"; "Hokku. A pigeon perches far below..."; "Hokku. On Coney Island I sat near the..."; "I cannot touch your strings..."; "I cracked the world down..."; "I ran down rivers that they could not run..."; "I spoke through the dream once,..."; "I take her. Triumph scatter..."; "I Walk the Road Againg"; "I walked down to the river once..."; "I will seek it out now:..."; "I wonder where she moves now..."; "Imperative, the crossing of a bridge..."; "Incidental Night Music for Robert Frost's Vermont"; "Incidnet in G. V."; "An indignant letter about Sanitation"; "Jornaux D'Orphee"; "Keep off the grass a thing in which..."; "The King of Harlem"; "Landscape"; "Leo's Birthday Poem"; "Lion Cubs"; "The Lexington Murder"; "A Long Thin Poem"; "Luchamos contra los Morros..."; "The man at the Post asked..."; "Marlin Night-Bound"; "The Meaning of Hype"; "Microcosmia"; "The mind is beautiful at rationalization. This..."; "Negroes II"; "An Oak Tree"; "...of the back street..."; "On the Dying of the Poet's Father by Cancer"; "Pastiche Among the Mushroomclouds"; "Perfect chord and barren woman..."; "Person: Friend"; "Poems published in 'The Rising Sun' vol 28 summer of 1957"; "Polynices"; "Pour Orphee"; "Proem"; "...put them there..."; "Quatrains"; "Reflection"; "Rebellion"; "De Religione Vera"; "Saduva"; "...same time and so he held it in his hand..."; "Sarcasm"; "Saw the vagrant, standing..."; "Seven Christmas Sonnets"; "smoke where he alone trods aimlessly..."; "So much clerical work..."; "Soliloquy for a Sunset"; "Something I've noticed from all..."; "The Song of Liadan"; "The Song of Songs which is Soloman's..."; "Sonnet after Rimbaud"; "Sous l'Arc de Triomphe"; "Sweeney Among the Mushroom Clouds"; "The sweet spring wind flung across the hill..."; "There, always clanging, ringing..."; "...there are..."; "The time comes when I cannot..."; "The turning field..."; "Upon the day before the witches revels..."; "...upward again, a dark cross on deep blue..."; "Villonelle Primitive"; "The War Game"; "The Water Witch"; "When the crystal headed serpent raised..."; "Wind - hokku"; "Winds: it is over. The evening is too..."; "The word is too much with us:..."; "The year a finite space, to freeze the..."; "You Can Sing"; "You couldn't have heard...".
      - Papers and notes, undated
        - Miscellaneous Papers and Manuscripts, undated (Box 7)
          Contains: typescript and holographic writings with corrections.
        - Notes, "Random Thoughts", undated (Box 7)
          Contains: typescript and holographic writings.
      - Works by others, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 7)
        Contains: typescripts (some with corrections) and holographic writings. Some are copies made by SRD. Includes: Baudelaire, Charles: "Au Lecteur"; Beal, Tita: "Soul-Spade"; Borak, Jeff: "Flight of the Thunderbird"; Colbath, Arnold: "Something About An Oyster"; Crites, Michael: 11 poems, 1 brown envelope to SRD, class attendance roster; Elitzik, Paul: "Against the Shore"; Giarraputo, Warren: "The Parade", "S'cuse Me One Thousand Seventeen", "Take It Or Leave It I'll Take It--I'll Take It"; Hacker, Marilyn: "The Terrible Children", "Evelyn Alone", 7 poems submitted to Poetry N.W., 3 poems written in London, "On Discovering that April 1 is Easter, 1961", "The Terrible Children", "This morning, dawn was like a...", "Only to Love I've Learned", "Dalilah"; Mistral, Gabriela: "Ruth"; Saland, Arnold: "The Arrow Beyond"; Sallis, Jane: "Tomorrow Will Be Different, Yesterday Was"; Tobey, Nancy: "Black of the Spectrum"; Warsh, Lewis: "The Door", "The Chapel" with critical essay fragment by SRD; Delany, Peggy: Review of "Greengage Summer" by Rumer Godden, Notes on last day of school.
    - Journals, 1958-01-1974
      - Samuel Delany, 1958-01-1974
        - Journal #1, 1958-01-1958-02 (Box 7)
        - Journal #2, 1959-01- (Box 7)
        - Journal #3, 1959-01- (Box 8)
        - Journal #4, 1959-04-1959-05 (Box 8)
        - Journal #5, 1959- (Box 8)
        - Journal #6, 1959- (Box 8)
        - Journal #7, 1959- (Box 8)
        - Journal #8, 1960-03- (Box 8)
        - Journal #9, 1960 Winter (Box 8)
        - Journal #10, 1960 Spring (Box 9)
        - Journal #11, 1960 Spring (Box 9)
        - Journal #12, 1960 inclusive to July (Box 9)
        - Journal #13, 1960-09- (Box 9)
        - Journal #14, 1960 Autumn (Box 9)
        - Journal #15, 1961-09-1961-10 (Box 10)
        - Journal #16, 1961 Spring, Summer (Box 10)
        - Journal #17, 1961 Summer (Box 10)
        - Journal #18, 1961-08- (Box 10)
        - Journal #19, 1961-11-1962-06 (Box 10)
        - Journal #20, 1962 Spring (Box 10)
        - Journal #21, 1962 Spring (Box 11)
        - Journal #22, 1962 Summer (Box 11)
        - Journal #23, 1962-11- (Box 11)
        - Journal #24, 1963 inclusive to January-February (Box 11)
        - Journal #25, 1963 inclusive through March (Box 11)
        - Journal #26, 1964-06-1964-07 (Box 11)
        - Journal #27, 1964-08- (Box 11)
        - Journal #28, 1964-09-1965-01 (Box 11)
        - Journal #29, 1965-06-1965-07 (Box 12)
        - Journal #30, 1965-12- (Box 12)
        - Journal #31, 1966-03- (Box 12)
        - Journal #32, 1967-07-1967-10 (Box 12)
        - Journal #33, 1967-12- (Box 13)
        - Journal #34, 1968-08- (Box 13)
        - Journal #35, 1968- (Box 13)
        - Journal #36, 1969-01-1969-02 (Box 13)
        - Journal #37, 1969-04- (Box 14)
        - Journal #38, 1969-06- (Box 14)
        - Journal #39, 1969-10- (Box 14)
          Includes: photoprints.
        - Journal #40, 1970-03-1970-06 (Box 14)
        - Journal #41, 1970-11-1970-12 (Box 14)
        - Journal #42, 1970-12-1971-01 (Box 14)
        - Journal #43, 1971-03-1971-04 (Box 14)
        - Journal #44, 1971-03-1971-09 (Box 15)
          Includes: photoprint.
        - Journal #45, 1971-10-1971-11 (Box 15)
        - Journal #46, 1971- (Box 15)
        - Journal #47, 1971-11-1972-02 (Box 15)
        - Journal #48, 1972-05- (Box 15)
        - Journal #49, 1972-10-1973-05 (Box 15)
          Includes: magazine clipping, printed pictures.
        - Journal #50, 1972- (Box 16)
          Includes: postcard, cartoon clipping.
        - Journal #51, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
        - Journal #52, 1973- (Box 16)
        - Journal #53, 1973- (Box 16)
        - Journal #54, 1973- (Box 16)
          Includes: printed picture.
        - Journal #55, 1973- (Box 16)
        - Journal #56, 1973- (Box 16)
          Includes: postcards, appointment card.
        - Journal #57, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #58, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #59, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #60, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #61, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #62, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #63, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #64, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #65, 1973- (Box 17)
        - Journal #66, 1974- (Box 18)
        - Journal #67, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #68, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #69, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #70, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #71, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #72, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #73, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #74, undated (Box 18)
        - Journal #75, undated (Box 19)
        - Journal #76, undated (Box 19)
        - Journal #77, undated (Box 19)
          Includes: printed picture, paper jacket for 'The Jewels of Aptor'.
        - Journal #78, undated (Box 19)
        - Journal #79, undated (Box 20)
        - Journal #80, undated (Box 20)
        - Journal #81, undated (Box 20)
        - Journal #82, undated (Box 20)
        - Journal #83, undated (Box 20)
        - Journal #84, undated (Box 21)
        - Journal #85, undated (Box 21)
        - Journal #86, undated (Box 21)
        - Journal #87, undated (Box 21)
        - Journal #88, undated (Box 21)
        - Journal #89, undated (Box 22)
        - Journal #90, undated (Box 22)
        - Journal #91, undated (Box 22)
        - Journal #92, undated (Box 22)
        - Journal #93, undated (Box 22)
          Includes: newspaper clipping, printed picture.
        - Journal #94, 1972- (Box 23)
          Includes: magazine and newspaper clippings.
        - Journal #95, undated (Box 23)
        - Journal #96, undated (Box 23)
        - Journal #97, undated (Box 23)
        - Journal #98, undated (Box 23)
        - Journal #99, undated (Box 23)
        - Journal #100, undated (Box 24)
      - "Bob's" Journal, undated
        - Journal #1 (Bob's?), undated (Box 16)
    - Dhalgren reviews & materials, circa 1975 (Box 25)
      Contains: reviews, including newspaper clippings, printed material, and photocopies; typescript draft fragment; corrections list; Ethos: Volume 8 Number 22.
    - School papers, 1956-1975
      - School papers: Bronx High School of Science, 1956-1960 (Box 25)
        Contains: school documents; schoolwork, including loose papers and workbook. Also includes: schoolwork by Peggy Delany (sister).
      - School papers: college, 1960-1975 (Box 25)
        Contains: schoolwork; school documents (1960-1962). Also includes: attendance sheets from professorship at SUNY Buffalo (1974-1975); application by Maragaret Boyd Delany.
    - Music, circa 1953 (Box 25)
      Contains: guitar lesson book; sheet music; loose pages with chords and/or lyrics.
    - Art, undated (Box 25)
      Contains: looseleaf drawing notebooks; crayon drawings; pen sketches; pencil sketches.
    - Printed material, 1957-1975
      - Magazines, 1957-1968-01
        - Math Bulletin, 1957-1959 (Box 26)
          Contains: 3 issues of Math Buelltin from Bronx High School of Science.
        - Info, circa 1961 (Box 26)
          Contains: "Info" high school pulication: volume XX no. 1 (October 1961) and bulletin no. 4 (undated).
        - Literary Cavalcade, 1958-05-1960-02 (Box 26)
          Contains: 4 issues of Literary Cavalcade.
        - Publications from Camp Rising Sun, 1958-1968-01 (Box 26)
          Contains: 4 issues of "The Sundial"; 4 issues of "The Winter Sun"; 9 issues of "The Rising Sun"; 1 issue of "Kallikanzaros".
      - Memorabilia, circa 1959-1975 (Box 26)
        Contains: The Fuller Brush Magazine; The Spectrum: Vol. 25, No. 63 (publication from SUNY Buffalo); notices and announcement posters; Showbill program: "The Trials of Oscar Wilde"; Stadium Concerts Review: vol. XLIII, no. 1; Greek Youth Hostels Association members card, Inernational Certificates of Vaccination as approved by W.H.O.; rejection slip; brown envelope; "You Are a 'Son-of-a-Humekey' Say I, The 'Son-of-a-Humegel'" by Motte A. Eber; paper bag with holographic note; picture cut out of a magazine; bookmark with holographic note; tag ad for "Fabritonic"; antique fire engine print in envelope; 10 picture cards/collages; notice from draft board; Middlebury College Bread Loaf Writers' Conference applications.
    - Financial records, 1960-1975 (Box 26)
      Contains: 14 checks; royalty statement; medical dosuments; bills; train ticket.
    - Tomorrow Symposium (S.F. conference), 1975- (Box 27)
      Contains: notes; announcement poster and registration form; correspondence re: Tomorrow Symposium.
    - Correspondence, 1957-1975
      - Correspondence in alphabetical order as arranged by SRD, 1959-1975; (4 folders) (Box 27)
        Contains: letters, notes, and postcards to and from: Avon Books (Mary Briggins); Bantam Books (Gloria Boykin, Sydny Weinberg, and Frederik Pohl); Block, Lawrence; Caruso, Paul; Clark, James; Davis, Hal; Delany, Mrs. Samuel R. (mother); Disch, Thomas; Ellison, Harlan; Fiedler, Leslie A.; Fischer, William (?); Gawron, Jean M.; Goldman, Arnold; Hacker, Marilyn (including letters to Hacker from others besides SRD); Halpern, Daniel; Hastings, Arthur; Landry, Harold; Last, Martin; Merrill, Judith; Morrison, Henry and Gail; Mugar Library at Boston University (Howard Gotlieb); Nicholls, Peter; Russ, Joanna; Sawyers, Linda; Wexler, Warren; White, Luise; Williams, Heathcote.
      - Correspondence arranged chronologically, 1957-1972; (2 folders) (Box 27)
        Contains: personal, business, and fan letters to and from SRD. Also includes: letter to Marilyn Hacker Delany not from SRD.
      - Correspondence arranged chronologically, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
        Contains: letters, notes, telegram, and memo to, from, and re: SRD. Includes: photocopy of pen sketch by Mia Wolff; fan letter from William Gibson.
      - Undated letters, rough drafts (Box 27)
        Contains: undated letters and notes to and from SRD; rough drafts of letters.
  - Materials deposited circa 1999, 1947-1999; 51.75; (52 boxes)